## **CONTACT INFO**

Cell: 0030 6983931901

Email: grigorisg3jobs@hotmail.com

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/grigoris-palaiochoritis/

GitHub:

https://github.com/GrigorisPs

Portfolio:

https://grigorisps.github.io/



GRIGORIS PALAIOCHORITIS
ENTRY LEVEL FULL STACK DEVELOPER

#### **PROFILE**

Being a career changer, I recently graduated from **PeopleCert Education Coding Bootcamp (Javascript)**. For the past 3 years I have been self-employed, providing food and drink services as a cafe owner. Running my own business, helped me build good sense of responsibility and multitasking was part of my everyday job. In order to stay competitive I had to be a fast learner and be motivated by setting new goals

#### **EDUCATION**

Oct 2020 - Apr 2021 AFDEmp PeopleCert Education Full Stack Development

- 500 hrs of intensive training in Software Development
- Object Oriented Programming, Functional Programming, Debugging Techniques, Test Driven Development, Common Architecture Patterns, Data/Class Modelling

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

PeopleCert Software Developer Skills (Foundation Level) PeopleCert Software Developer Skills (Advanced Level)

## **LANGUAGES**

Greek - Native English - B2

## Military obligations fullfilled

#### **SKILLS**

- JavaScript, Typescript, Node.js, Express.js, Sails.js /Waterline,
- Web MVC
- SQL MySQL
- HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap, jQuery, React, Angular Git, XML, RESTful API

## **PROJECTS**

# Individual Project Netflix-clone

- Next/s, React/s, Javascript
- Firebase, Auth, Stripe
- REST routes, HTTP status codes
- HTML, CSS, TailwindCss

#### **PROIECTS**

## **Group Project**

VideoClub - eBook

User signup - login

- Different user roles
- Ability to connect to a database
- Product filtering
- Real-time chat socketIO
- Payment process PayPal checkout (sandbox)
- Sails.js
- Sass

### **CAREER SUMMARY**

**Self-Employed Cafe Owner** 

Old Villager | May 2019 - January 2023

**System Administrator Assistant** 

Wizznet Station | Apr 2018 - May 2019